A Guide to the John A. Hartford Foundation records, Grants, Series 8 FA1416
Rockefeller Archive Center
- On Lok Senior Health Services, Implementation of a Multi-Site Initiative for Risk-Based Long-Term Care, Evaluation Site Visit, Marie-Louise Ansak, John Shen (91045-G), 1991-1992 (Box 578, Folder 4279)
- On Lok Senior Health Services, PACE (Program of All-Inclusive Care for the Elderly) Service Development Conference, Minutes, 1991 (Box 578, Folder 4279)
- On Lok Senior Health Services, PACE (Program of All-Inclusive Care for the Elderly) Public Policy Forum, 1992 (Box 578, Folder 4280)
- On Lok Senior Health Services, PACE (Program of All-Inclusive Care for the Elderly) Forum, 1992-1993 (Box 578, Folder 4282)
- On Lok Senior Health Services, Health Care Financing Administration (HCFA) Evaluation, 1991 (Box 578, Folder 4284)
- On Lok Senior Health Services, Interdisciplinary Training for Comprehensive Care for the Elderly (Geriatric Interdisciplinary Team Training [GITT] Planning), Jennie Chin Hansen (95205-G), 1993, 1995-1997, 1999-2001 (Box 578, Folder 4285)
- On Lok Senior Health Services, Interdisciplinary Training for Comprehensive Care for the Elderly (Geriatric Interdisciplinary Team Training [GITT] Planning), Jennie Chin Hansen (95205-G), 1993, 1995-1997, 1999-2001 (Box 579, Folder 4286-4287)
- On Lok Senior Health Services, Interdisciplinary Training for Comprehensive Care for the Elderly (Geriatric Interdisciplinary Team Training [GITT] Planning), Site Visit, Jennie Chin Hansen (95205-G), 1995-1996 (Box 579, Folder 4288)
- On Lok Senior Health Services, Geriatric Interdisciplinary Team Training (GITT), Jennie Chin Hansen (96203-G), 1996-2000 (Box 579, Folder 4289-4291)
- On Lok Senior Health Services, Geriatric Interdisciplinary Team Training (GITT), Jennie Chin Hansen (96203-G), 1996-2000 (Box 580, Folder 4292-4294)
- On Lok Senior Health Services, Geriatric Interdisciplinary Team Training (GITT), Jennie Chin Hansen (96203-G), 1997-1998 (Box 580, Folder 4295-4296)
- On Lok Senior Health Services, Geriatric Interdisciplinary Team Training (GITT), Site Visit, Jennie Chin Hansen (96203-G), 1996-1997 (Box 580, Folder 4297)
- On Lok Senior Health Services, Geriatric Interdisciplinary Team Training (GITT), Site Visit, Jennie Chin Hansen (96203-G), 1996-1997 (Box 581, Folder 4298)
- On Lok Senior Health Services, Geriatric Interdisciplinary Team Training (GITT), EMRIE, Site Visit, Jennie Chin Hansen (96203-G), 1996-1997 (Box 581, Folder 4299-4300)
- On Lok Senior Health Services, Geriatric Interdisciplinary Team Training (GITT), Site Visit, Jennie Chin Hansen (96203-G), 1998 (Box 581, Folder 4301-4302)
- On Lok Senior Health Services, Geriatric Interdisciplinary Team Training (GITT), Article, Jennie Chin Hansen (96203-G), 2000 (Box 581, Folder 4303)
- Pace University, To Expand and Enhance Pace University's Public School Partnerships, Mary M. Versteck (94373-O), 1994-1995 (Box 581, Folder 4304)
- Rush-Presbyterian-St. Luke's Medical Center, Geriatric Interdisciplinary Team Training (GITT), Denis A. Evans (95211-G), 1995-1998 (Box 581, Folder 4305-4306)
- Rush-Presbyterian-St. Luke's Medical Center, Geriatric Interdisciplinary Team Training (GITT), Denis A. Evans (95211-G), 1995-1998 (Box 582, Folder 4307)
- Rush-Presbyterian-St. Luke's Medical Center, Geriatric Interdisciplinary Team Training (GITT), Denis A. Evans (96207-G), 1996-2000 (Box 582, Folder 4308-4311)
- Rush-Presbyterian-St. Luke's Medical Center, Geriatric Interdisciplinary Team Training (GITT), Trip Files, Denis A. Evans (96207-G), 1996-1997 (Box 582, Folder 4312)
- Rush-Presbyterian-St. Luke's Medical Center, Geriatric Interdisciplinary Team Training (GITT), Trip Files-Site Visit, Denis A. Evans (96207-G), 1998 (Box 582, Folder 4313)
- United Health Services System Case Management, Proposal, 1992 (Box 583, Folder 4314)
- United Health Services System Case Management, Final Report, 1996 (Box 583, Folder 4315)
- University of California, Los Angeles (UCLA), Improving the Appropriateness of Medication Prescribing in Nursing Homes, Mark H. Beers (89028-3G), 1989-1996 (Box 583, Folder 4316-4319)
  - University of California, Los Angeles (UCLA), Improving the Appropriateness of Medication Prescribing in Nursing Homes, Mark H. Beers (89028-3G), Nursing Home Medication Review Program, 1990 (Box 583, Folder 4317)
    Separated Materials
    Floppy disk
- University of California, Los Angeles (UCLA), Improving the Appropriateness of Medication Prescribing in Nursing Homes, Reports, Mark H. Beers (89028-3G), 1989-1990 (Box 583, Folder 4320)
- University of California, Los Angeles (UCLA), Improving the Appropriateness of Medication Prescribing in Nursing Homes, Site Visit, Mark H. Beers (89028-3G), 1989 (Box 584, Folder 4321)
- University of California, Los Angeles (UCLA), Improving the Appropriateness of Medication Prescribing in Nursing Homes, Site Visit, 1990 December 17 & 1992 June 22, Mark H. Beers (89028-3G), 1989-1992 (Box 584, Folder 4322)
- University of California, Los Angeles (UCLA), Improving the Appropriateness of Medication Prescribing in Nursing Homes, Evaluation, Mark H. Beers (89028-3G), 1990, 1992 (Box 584, Folder 4323)
- University of California, Los Angeles (UCLA), School of Medicine, Hartford Residency Geriatrics Training Program, Alan Fogelman (94143-G), 1994-1999 (Box 584, Folder 4324-4327)
- University of California, Los Angeles (UCLA), School of Medicine, Hartford Residency Geriatrics Training Program, Alan Fogelman (94143-G), 1994-1999 (Box 585, Folder 4328)
- University of California, Los Angeles (UCLA), School of Medicine, Hartford Residency Geriatrics Training Program, Miscellaneous, Alan Fogelman (94143-G), 1990, 1993-1995 (Box 585, Folder 4329-4330)
- University of California, Los Angeles (UCLA), School of Medicine, Hartford Residency Geriatrics Training Program, Site Visit, Alan Fogelman (94143-G), 1996 (Box 585, Folder 4331)
- University of California, Los Angeles (UCLA), School of Medicine, Hartford Residency Geriatrics Training Program, Evaluation, Alan Fogelman (94143-G), 1994-1998 (Box 585, Folder 4332-4334)
- University of California, San Francisco (UCSF), Center of Excellence, Seth Landefeld (97299-G), 1996-2001 (Box 585, Folder 4335)
- University of California, San Francisco (UCSF), Center of Excellence, Seth Landefeld (97299-G), 1996-2001 (Box 586, Folder 4336-4337)
- University of California, San Francisco (UCSF), Center of Excellence, UCSF Foundation, Seth Landefeld (97299-G), 2000 (Box 586, Folder 4338)
- University of Chicago, Early Detection, Evaluation and Treatment of Delirium in the Hospitalized Elderly, Christine Cassel (89015-3G), 1989-1992 (Box 586, Folder 4339-4340)
- University of Chicago, Geriatrics in Primary Care Training Initiative, Greg A. Sachs (94155-G), 1994-1998 (Box 586, Folder 4341)
- University of Chicago, Geriatrics in Primary Care Training Initiative, Greg A. Sachs (94155-G), 1994-1998 (Box 587, Folder 4342)
- American Academy of Family Physicians, Improving Geriatric Medicine in Community Hospital Family Practice Residency Programs, Gregg Warshaw (94330-G), 1994-1999 (Box 587, Folder 4343-4346)
- American Federation for Aging Research (AFAR), Medical Student Geriatrics Scholars Program, Stephanie Lederman (93331-G), 1993-1998 (Box 587, Folder 4347)
- American Federation for Aging Research (AFAR), Medical Student Geriatrics Scholars Program, Stephanie Lederman (93331-G), 1993-1998 (Box 588, Folder 4348-4351)
  - American Federation for Aging Research (AFAR), Medical Student Geriatrics Scholars Program, Stephanie Lederman (93331-G), 2017:003:001 (Box SF1)
    AFAR Sign
- American Federation for Aging Research (AFAR), Medical Student Geriatrics Scholars Program, Grantee Conference, Stephanie Lederman (93331-G), 1996 (Box 588, Folder 4352)
- American Federation for Aging Research (AFAR), Medical Student Geriatrics Scholars Program, Annual Meeting, Stephanie Lederman (93331-G), 1997 (Box 588, Folder 4353)
- American Federation for Aging Research (AFAR), Medical Student Geriatrics Scholars Program, Fellowship Meeting, Stephanie Lederman (93331-G), 1998-1999 (Box 588, Folder 4354)
- American Federation for Aging Research (AFAR), Medical Student Geriatrics Scholars Program, Abstracts & Reports, Stephanie Lederman (93331-G), 1994, 1996 (Box 588, Folder 4355-4356)
- American Federation for Aging Research (AFAR), Medical Student Geriatrics Scholars Program, Paul G. Beeson Scholars, Meeting, Stephanie Lederman (93331-G), 1996 (Box 589, Folder 4357-4358)
- California Pacific Medical Center, Senior Care Connections, Janeane Randolph (92072-G), 1985-1986, 1988-1989, 1991-1997 (Box 589, Folder 4359-4362)
- California Pacific Medical Center, Senior Care Connections, Janeane Randolph (92072-G), 1985-1986, 1988-1989, 1991-1997 (Box 590, Folder 4363)
- California Pacific Medical Center, Senior Care Connections, Report, Janeane Randolph (92072-G), 1992-1994 (Box 590, Folder 4364-4366)
- California Pacific Medical Center, Senior Care Connections, Site Visit, Janeane Randolph (92072-G), 1993 (Box 590, Folder 4367)
- California Pacific Medical Center, Senior Care Connections, Geriatric Collaborative Pratice Procedure Manual, Janeane Randolph (92072-G), 1993 April (Box 590, Folder 4368)
- California Pacific Medical Center, Senior Care Connections, Miscellaneous, Janeane Randolph (92072-G), 1992, 1994-1995 (Box 591, Folder 4369)
- California Pacific Medical Center, Senior Care Connections, Site Visit, Janeane Randolph (92072-G), 1993, 1996 (Box 591, Folder 4370)
- California Pacific Medical Center, Senior Care Connections, Final Report, Janeane Randolph (92072-G), 1996 (Box 591, Folder 4371-4373)
- California Pacific Medical Center, Senior Care Connections, Janeane Randolph (92072-G), 1997 (Box 591, Folder 4374)
- California Pacific Medical Center, Contract with Technology Assessment Group, 1992 (Box 591, Folder 4375)
- Carle Foundation Hospital, A Generalist Physician Based Model for Geriatric Collaborative Practice, Cheryl Schraeder (92123-G), 1992-1997 (Box 592, Folder 4376-4379)
- Carle Foundation Hospital, A Generalist Physician Based Model for Geriatric Collaborative Practice, Final Report, Cheryl Shraeder (92123-G), 1996 (Box 592, Folder 4380)
- Carle Foundation Hospital, A Generalist Physician Based Model for Geriatric Collaborative Practice, Progress Reports, Cheryl Shraeder (92123-G), 1993 (Box 592, Folder 4381-4382)
- Carle Foundation Hospital, A Generalist Physician Based Model for Geriatric Collaborative Practice, Satisfaction Surveys, Cheryl Shraeder (92123-G), 1995 (Box 593, Folder 4383)
- Carle Foundation Hospital, A Generalist Physician Based Model for Geriatric Collaborative Practice, Carle Clinical Studies, Cheryl Shraeder (92123-G), 1992 (Box 593, Folder 4384)
- Carle Foundation Hospital, A Generalist Physician Based Model for Geriatric Collaborative Practice, Evaluation, Cheryl Shraeder (92123-G), 1993, 1996 (Box 593, Folder 4385)
- Carle Foundation Hospital, A Generalist Physician Based Model for Geriatric Collaborative Practice, Site Visit, Cheryl Shraeder (92123-G), 1993 (Box 593, Folder 4386)
- Carle Foundation Hospital, Extension of A Generalist Physician Based Model for Geriatric Collaborative Practice, Cheryl Shraeder (92123-G), 1992, 1995-1996 (Box 593, Folder 4387)
- Case Western Reserve University, Centers of Excellence Designation Awards, Jerome Kowal (97258-G), 1997-2000, 2002 (Box 593, Folder 4388)
- Mt. Sinai Medical Center, Geriatrics Interdisciplinary Team Training (GITT) Partnership, Christine K. Cassel (95203-G), 1995-1998, 2000 (Box 593, Folder 4389-4391)
- Mt. Sinai Medical Center, Geriatrics Interdisciplinary Team Training (GITT) Partnership, Visit, Christine K. Cassel (95203-G), 1996 (Box 593, Folder 4392)
- Mt. Sinai Medical Center, Geriatrics Interdisciplinary Team Training (GITT) Partnership, Christine K. Cassel (96205-G), 1996-2001 (Box 594, Folder 4393-4397)
- Mt. Sinai Medical Center, Geriatrics Interdisciplinary Team Training (GITT) Partnership, Appendix I-K, Christine K. Cassel (96205-G), 1996 (Box 594, Folder 4398)
- Mt. Sinai Medical Center, Geriatrics Interdisciplinary Team Training (GITT) Partnership, Appendix I-K, Christine K. Cassel (96205-G), 1996 (Box 595, Folder 4399)
- Mt. Sinai Medical Center, Geriatrics Interdisciplinary Team Training (GITT) Partnership, Publications, Christine K. Cassel (96205-G), 1993, 1995, 1999 (Box 594, Folder 4400)
- Mt. Sinai Medical Center, Center of Excellence, Christine K. Cassel (96205-G), 1997-2000 (Box 595, Folder 4401-4402)
- Mt. Sinai Medical Center, Geriatric Medications Information for Practicing Physicians, Rosanne M. Leipzig (98169-G), 1998-2001 (Box 595, Folder 4403)
- Mt. Sinai Medical Center, Center of Excellence, Christine K. Cassel (990342), 1999-2004 (Box 595, Folder 4404)
- Mt. Sinai Medical Center, Center of Excellence, Christine K. Cassel (990342), 1999-2004 (Box 596, Folder 4405-4406)
- Mt. Sinai Medical Center of Greater Miami, Intervention Pathways to Integrate Eldercare Through Generalist Physician Offices, Gloria B. Weinberg (93134-G), 1993-1997 (Box 596, Folder 4407-4409)
- Mt. Sinai Medical Center of Greater Miami, Intervention Pathways to Integrate Eldercare Through Generalist Physician Offices, Gloria B. Weinberg (93134-G), 1993-1994 (Box 596, Folder 4410)
- Mt. Sinai Medical Center of Greater Miami, Intervention Pathways to Integrate Eldercare Through Generalist Physician Offices, Program Report Addendums, Gloria B. Weinberg (93134-G), 1993-1995 (Box 597, Folder 4411-4412)
- Mt. Sinai Medical Center of Greater Miami, Intervention Pathways to Integrate Eldercare Through Generalist Physician Offices, Evaluation, Gloria B. Weinberg (93134-G), 1994-1995 (Box 597, Folder 4413)
- Mt. Sinai Medical Center of Greater Miami, Intervention Pathways to Integrate Eldercare Through Generalist Physician Offices, Gloria B. Weinberg (93134-G) (Box 597, Folder 4414)
- Mt. Sinai Medical Center of Greater Miami, Intervention Pathways to Integrate Eldercare Through Generalist Physician Offices, Gloria B. Weinberg (96130-G), 1996-1998 (Box 597, Folder 4415)
- Mt. Sinai Medical Center of Greater Miami, Intervention Pathways to Integrate Eldercare Through Generalist Physician Offices, Evaluation, Gloria B. Weinberg (96130-G), 1993, 1995-1998 (Box 597, Folder 4416)
- Arizona State University, Enhancing Successful Generalist Physician Project Implementation and Program Impact, Frank G. Williams (94026-G), 1994-1996 (Box 597, Folder 4417-4418)
- Arizona State University, Enhancing Successful Generalist Physician Project Implementation and Program Impact, Frank G. Williams (94026-G), 1994-1998 (Box 598, Folder 4419)
- Arizona State University, Enhancing Successful Generalist Physician Project Implementation and Program Impact, Foreword for the Book, Frank G. Williams (94026-G), 1997 (Box 598, Folder 4420)
- Arizona State University, Enhancing Successful Generalist Physician Project Implementation and Program Impact, Conference, Frank G. Williams (94026-G), 1993-1997 (Box 598, Folder 4421-4424)
- Arizona State University, Enhancing Successful Generalist Physician Project Implementation and Program Impact, Progress Report, Frank G. Williams (94026-G), 1994 (Box 598, Folder 4425)
- Arizona State University, Enhancing Successful Generalist Physician Project Implementation and Program Impact, Progress Report, Frank G. Williams (94026-G), 1994, 1996 (Box 599, Folder 4426-4428)
- Arizona State University, Enhancing Successful Generalist Physician Project Implementation and Program Impact, Final Report, Frank G. Williams (94026-G), 1996 (Box 599, Folder 4429)
- Arizona State University, Enhancing Generalist Program Impact, Frank G. Williams (96124-G), 1995-2000 (Box 599, Folder 4432)
- Arizona State University, Enhancing Generalist Program Impact, Frank G. Williams (96124-G), 1995-2000 (Box 600, Folder 4431-4432)
- Arizona State University, Enhancing Generalist Program Impact, Progress Report, Frank G. Williams (96124-G), 1996-1997 (Box 600, Folder 4433-4435)
- Arizona State University, Enhancing Generalist Program Impact, Progress Report, Frank G. Williams (96124-G), 1997-1999 (Box 601, Folder 4436-4440)
  - Arizona State University, Enhancing Generalist Program Impact, Progress Report, Frank G. Williams (96124-G), 2014:003:003, 2014:003:004, 2014:003:005, 2014:003:006
    Audio material 4 tapes-Conference tapes
- Arizona State University, Enhancing Generalist Program Impact, Progress Report, Frank G. Williams (96124-G), 1999 (Box 602, Folder 4441-4443)
- Arizona State University, Enhancing Generalist Program Impact, Subcontract Details, Frank G. Williams (96124-G), 1996-1997 (Box 602, Folder 4444)
- Arizona State University, Enhancing Generalist Program Impact, Reports, Frank G. Williams (96124-G), 2000 (Box 602, Folder 4445-4446)
- Arizona State University, Enhancing Generalist Program Impact, Reports, Frank G. Williams (96124-G), 2000 (Box 603, Folder 4447)
- Baylor College of Medicine, Center of Excellence, Robert J. Luchi (97204-G), 1997-2001 (Box 603, Folder 4448-4452)
- Baylor College of Medicine, Center of Excellence, Robert J. Luchi (97204-G), 1998-2000 (Box 604, Folder 4453-4454)
- Cold Spring Harbor Laboratory, The Biology of Long-Term Memory, Timothy P. Tully (96093-G), 1996-2000, 2003 (Box 604, Folder 4455-4458)
- Cold Spring Harbor Laboratory, The Biology of Long-Term Memory, Additional Progress Material, Timothy P. Tully (96093-G), 1998-1999 (Box 604, Folder 4459)
- Cold Spring Harbor Laboratory, The Biology of Long-Term Memory, Miscellaneous, Timothy P. Tully (96093-G), 1995, 1997-1998 (Box 605, Folder 4460)
- Cold Spring Harbor Laboratory, The Biology of Long-Term Memory, Timothy P. Tully (96093-G), 1996 (Box 605, Folder 4461-4462)
- Cold Spring Harbor Laboratory, The Biology of Long-Term Memory, Evaluation, Timothy P. Tully (96093-G), 1996-1998 (Box 605, Folder 4463)
- Cold Spring Harbor Laboratory, The Biology of Long-Term Memory, 1996 Annual Report, Timothy P. Tully (96093-G), 1997 (Box 605, Folder 4464)
- University of Minnesota, Geriatrics Interdisciplinary Team Training (GITT), Robert L. Kane (95222-G), 1995-1997, 2000 (Box 605, Folder 4465-4466)
- University of Minnesota, Geriatrics Interdisciplinary Team Training (GITT), Robert L. Kane (95222-G), 1996 (Box 606, Folder 4467-4468)
- University of Minnesota, Geriatrics Interdisciplinary Team Training (GITT), Report, Robert L. Kane (95222-G), 1993 (Box 606, Folder 4469)
- University of Minnesota, Geriatrics Interdisciplinary Team Training (GITT), Miscellaneous Annual Reports, Robert L. Kane (95222-G), 1994-1996 (Box 606, Folder 4470)
- University of Minnesota, Geriatrics Interdisciplinary Team Training (GITT), Robert L. Kane (96210-G), 1996-2001 (Box 606, Folder 4471-4472)
- University of Minnesota, Geriatrics Interdisciplinary Team Training (GITT), Evaluation, Robert L. Kane (96210-G), 1995-1998 (Box 606, Folder 4473)
- University of Minnesota, Geriatrics Interdisciplinary Team Training (GITT), Progress Report, Robert L. Kane (962120-G), 1998 (Box 607, Folder 4474)
- University of North Carolina, Geriatrics Interdisciplinary Team Training (GITT), Mark E. Williams (952221-G), 1994-1997 (Box 607, Folder 4475-4476)
- University of North Carolina, Geriatrics Interdisciplinary Team Training (GITT), Interdisciplinary Approaches to the Care of Rural Elders, Site Visit, Mark E. Williams (952221-G), 1997-1999 (Box 607, Folder 4477-4479)
- University of North Carolina, Geriatrics Interdisciplinary Team Training (GITT), Interdisciplinary Approaches to the Care of Rural Elders, Mark E. Williams (952221-G), 1997, 1999-2000 (Box 608, Folder 4480-4481)
- University of Rochester School of Medicine and Dentistry, Center of Excellence, William J. Hall (97245-G), 1997-2002 (Box 608, Folder 4482-4483)
- University of Rochester School of Medicine and Dentistry, Center of Excellence, Site Visit, William J. Hall (97245-G), 1998-2000 (Box 608, Folder 4484)
- University of South Florida, Geriatrics Interdisciplinary Team Training (GITT), Eric Pfeiffer (95210-G), 1995-1998, 2000 (Box 608, Folder 4485)
- University of South Florida, Geriatrics Interdisciplinary Team Training (GITT), Eric Pfeiffer (96211-G), 1996-2000 (Box 609, Folder 4486-4489)
- University of South Florida, Geriatrics Interdisciplinary Team Training (GITT), Site Visit, Eric Pfeiffer (96211-G), 1997-1999 (Box 609, Folder 4490)
- University of South Florida, Geriatrics Interdisciplinary Team Training (GITT), Reprints, Eric Pfeiffer (96211-G), 1996, 1999 (Box 609, Folder 4491)
- University of Kansas Medical Center, Center of Excellence, Stephanie A. Studenski (97270-G), 1997-2001 (Box 609, Folder 4492)
- University of Kansas Medical Center, Center of Excellence, Stephanie A. Studenski (97270-G), 1997-2001 (Box 610, Folder 4493-4494)
- University of Kansas Medical Center, Center of Excellence, Foundation Survey, Stephanie A. Studenski (97270-G), 1997 (Box 610, Folder 4495)
- University of Kansas Medical Center, Center of Excellence, Site Visit, Stephanie A. Studenski (97270-G), 1997 (Box 610, Folder 4496)
- University of Kansas Medical Center, Center of Excellence, Trip File, Stephanie A. Studenski (97270-G), 1998-2000 (Box 610, Folder 4497)
- University of Maryland, Expanding the National Network for Intergenerational Health, Daniel Leviton (97089-G), 1997-2001 (Box 610, Folder 4498-4499)
- University of Maryland, Expanding the National Network for Intergenerational Health, Daniel Leviton (97089-G), 1997-2001 (Box 611, Folder 4500-4502)
- University of Maryland, Expanding the National Network for Intergenerational Health, Staff Evaluation, Daniel Leviton (97089-G), 1998 (Box 611, Folder 4503)
- University of Maryland, Expanding the National Network for Intergenerational Health, Adult Health & Development Program (AHDP) Manual, Daniel Leviton (97089-G), 1998 (Box 611, Folder 4504)
- University of Maryland, National Network for Intergenerational Health: Organizational Development Plan, Daniel Leviton (2000-0441), 1996, 1999-2002 (Box 611, Folder 4505)
- University of Maryland, National Network for Intergenerational Health: Organizational Development Plan, Daniel Leviton (2000-0441), 1996, 1999-2002 (Box 612, Folder 4506)
- University of Michigan, Center of Excellence, Jeffrey B. Halter (97203-G), 1997-2001 (Box 612, Folder 4507-4508)
- University of Washington School of Medicine, Center of Excellence, Itamar B. Abrass (97202-G), 1997-2001 (Box 612, Folder 4509)
- Yale University, School of Medicine, Center of Excellence, Mary E. Tinetti (97266-G), 1997-2002 (Box 612, Folder 4510-4511)
- Yale University, School of Medicine, Prevention of Functional Decline in the Hospitalized Elderly, Interim Progress Report, Sharon K. Inouye, 1989-1991 (Box 613, Folder 4512-4517)
- The American Geriatrics Society (AGS), Increasing Geriatrics Expertise in Non-Primary Care Specialists, Dennis Jahnigen (93351-G), 1993-1999 (Box 614, Folder 4518-4519)
- The American Geriatrics Society (AGS), Increasing Geriatrics Expertise in Non-Primary Care Specialists, Advisory Board, Dennis Jahnigen (93351-G), 1994 (Box 614, Folder 4520)
- The American Geriatrics Society (AGS), Increasing Geriatrics Expertise in Non-Primary Care Specialists, Evaluation, Dennis Jahnigen (93351-G), 1994 (Box 614, Folder 4521)
- The American Geriatrics Society (AGS), Increasing Geriatrics Expertise in Non-Primary Care Specialists, Interim Progress Report, Dennis Jahnigen (93351-G), 1995-1996 (Box 614, Folder 4522-4523)
- The American Geriatrics Society (AGS), Increasing Geriatrics Expertise in Non-Primary Care Specialists, Site Visit, 1996 November 4, Dennis Jahnigen (93351-G), 1994-1996 (Box 614, Folder 4524)
- The American Geriatrics Society (AGS), Increasing Geriatrics Expertise in Non-Primary Care Specialists, Site Visit, 1996 November 4, Dennis Jahnigen (93351-G), 1994-1996 (Box 615, Folder 4525-4526)